Guide to the David A. Clarke papers, 1974-1997 MS2010
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Part 2 (donated 1997-2000), 1974-1997; Series 2; 129 Linear Feet
  - Subject files, 1977-1997; Series 2 Subseries 2
    - Board of education election, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 36)
    - Board of Trade, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Board of Trade, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Board of Trade Legislative Steering Committee, 1985 January 11; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Board of Trade, Brussels, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Boards and Commissions, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Bobby [Prohibition of Horse Drawn Carriages], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Bobby King, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 27)
    - Boll, James, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Boonsprasirt, Suganya, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Boonyakit and Graut, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Bou, Edward C., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Boy Scouts of America, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Boys and Girls Club, Greater Washington, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Brady letter, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Brenda Dudley, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Bribery and graft, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Brochure, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Brochures, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Brochures [death penalty], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Broganza, M., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Browning-Ferris Industries, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Brussels Accord, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Brussels Accord, 1993; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Brussels Accord, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Brussels Press, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Brussels Task Force, 1985; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Brussels task force, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Brussels Trade Fair, Washington Convention Center, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Brussels Washington Accord, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Budget, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Budget, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 25)
    - Budget, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Budget [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Budget [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Budget [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Budget [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Budget [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Budget [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Budget [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Budget [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Budget [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Budget [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Budget 1989, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - Budget calendar, 1994 November-1994 December; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Budget charts, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Budget generally, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 17)
    - Budget letters, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Budget meeting with members, 1994 November 23; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Budget memo from Clarke to members, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Budget submission resolution, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Bunker Hill Elementary School Project, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Business plan, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Business return mail, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Business to Business Economic Development Conference Advisory Board, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Cal Thomas, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 43)
    - Calculated rates, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Calculated Real Property Tax, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Caldwell, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Caldwell, John, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - California trip, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Calls, 1986; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Calvary Baptist Church, general, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - CAN Obligation Bond Authenticity Act, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - Cancer education for D.C. health and science teachers, 1983 June 15; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Candon, Mary Eva, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Capital City Magazine, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Capital Committee, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Capitol Hill Tax Payers Alliance, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Carriage horse correspondence, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Carriage horse legislation, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Carriage horse testimony, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - Carter campaign, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Carter, Dickie S., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Carver Terrace Tenants Association, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Cash, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Catina Reed, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - CBS, New York City, 1988 May 12; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Celebrity invitations, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Census, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 28)
    - Central and East European Law Initiative, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Certificates, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Chagnon, John J., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Chairman Clarke's Comprehensive Platform to Tackle Fiscal Crisis, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Chairman Clarke's Mortgaged Future, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Chairman David Clarke (Legislative Agenda), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Chairman David Clarke, Prison Industries, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Chairman, Financial Disclosure Statement, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Chairman's Inaugural Remarks, 1983 January 3; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Chairman's Statement on Submission of FY 1986 Budget, 1985 February 01; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Chairman's Transition Fund, 1991; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1983 October 06; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Chamber of Commerce, D.C., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Charles Profitt, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Charles Sherman, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 21)
    - Charles Walker, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Charles, Bob, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Children's Hospital, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Children's Hospital, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Children's Island, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Christ House -- Health care, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Cisneros, Mary, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Citizen correspondence, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - City Administrator, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - City Council, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - City Paper, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 12)
    - Citywide statistical survey, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 29)
    - Civilian Complaint Review Board, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - Clarence Brandley, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Clark, Richard, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Clarke -- inaugural committee assignments, 1983; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Clarke Amendment, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Clarke personal odds and ends, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Clarke press releases, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Clarke press releases, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 30)
    - Clarke statement re: RFK Stadium incident, 1984 January 08; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 49)
    - Clarke testimony before D.C. Correctional Facility Study Commission, 1985 October 28; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Clarke to Barry budget correspondence, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Clarke v. DPC [traffic incident] -- working, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Clarke v. DPW [traffic incident], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Clavens, Angela (Office Record on the Measure), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Clement Gofhamodimo, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Clergy letter, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Clinton Gore transition, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Clippings, 1984 November; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 26)
    - Clippings, 1984 December; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 27)
    - Clippings -- Bail, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 17)
    - Clippings -- Bill 3-245 District of Columbia Midwifery Practice Act of 1979, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 39)
    - Clippings -- Chairman, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Clippings -- Convention Center, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 36)
    - Clippings -- Council memoranda, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 34)
    - Clippings -- D.C. Realtors/good government, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 46)
    - Clippings -- EA 3-124 Emergency Rental Housing Conversion Regulation Act of 1980, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - Clippings -- EA 3-130 Unemployment Compensation Act Emergency Amendments of 1980, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 37)
    - Clippings -- EA 3-56 Second Emergency Home Purchase Assistance Fund Expansion Act of 1979, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Clippings -- Firefighters, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Clippings -- Gambling, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - Clippings -- Home rule, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Clippings -- Homeless/evictions, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Clippings -- KKK, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Clippings -- League of Cities, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 38)
    - Clippings -- media general, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Clippings -- Medicaid/hospital/welfare, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 40)
    - Clippings -- Minority contractors, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 41)
    - Clippings -- Monument/Norman Mayer, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 42)
    - Clippings -- National Airport crash/metro, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 43)
    - Clippings -- Population statistics, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Clippings -- Realtors/AOBA/"HIT", undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 47)
    - Clippings -- Reorganization, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 28)
    - Clippings -- School board elections/education, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 29)
    - Clippings -- Sexual assault, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 30)
    - Clippings -- Statehood/Constitutional Convention, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 31)
    - Clippings -- Street vendors, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 32)
    - Clippings -- Transition, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 33)
    - Clippings -- Ward One -- miscellaneous, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 35)
    - Clippings -- Washington Post/"Jimmy", undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - Clippings [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Clippings [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - Clippings [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 18)
    - Clippings [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 44)
    - Clippings [unlabeled], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 76, Folder 45)
    - Clippings notebook, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Clippings scrapbooks, 1974-1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 92, Box-folder 1)
    - CM notes, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Coalition of Housing Cooperatives, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Coalition on Death Penalty, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Coates, James, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Coe, Douglas E., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Co-Generation Facilities Emergency Act of 1993, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Colleagues, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Commissioners' notebook, 1990; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Committee Against All Killing, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Committee Against All Killing BOEE, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Committee for Strict Liability, Intervenor, Bliley v. Kelley, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Committee of 100 on the Federal City, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Committee of the Whole, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Housing, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Committee on Human Services public hearing [assault weapons], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Public Services, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Committee on Public Services, 1989 May 30; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Committee on Public Services, 1989 June 16; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Committee on Public Services, 1989 June 22; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Public Services, 1989 May 30; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Committee on Public Services, Del Price, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Committee on Self Determination, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Committee Print, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Committee Reorganization Plan, 1996; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Committee reports, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Committees, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Common Cause, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Community for Creative Non-Violence, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Comparison of D.C. taxes and spending to other local governments, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Comprehensive Merit Personnel Act of 1978, D.C., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - Comprehensive Plan, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Comprehensive Plan, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Comprehensive Plan, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Comprehensive Plan, 1994; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Comprehensive Settlement, Local 722, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Conference on Juvenile Delinquency, 1983 May 20; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Conference on Maintaining Municipal Integrity, Baltimore, MD, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Conflict of Interest Statement, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Congratulations -- Victory 1994, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Congress, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Congress, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Congress of the United States, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - Congress: Long Arm Jurisdiction, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Congressional, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 40)
    - Congressional legislation, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Congressional testimony, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Congressional testimony -- Chairman, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - Connecticut Avenue Association, 1983 June 08; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Consultations, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Consultations, 1993; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 27)
    - Consultations, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Consultations, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Consultations, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Contracting, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Contributions, 1982; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Convention Center, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Convention Center, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Convention Center Resolution, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Convention of D.C. Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1983 May 16; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Conventional Center management contract, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Conyers, William T., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Cook Stadium, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Cooke, Jack Kent, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Cooper, Anthony, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Cooper, Jerry (Constituent Service Fund Report), undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Cooperative purchasing, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Coppola, Frank, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Cornerstone, D.C., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Corporation Counsel, Office of, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Corporation Counsel's brief [Atkinson v. DC BOEE], 1991; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Corporation Counsel's brief [Atkinson v. DC BOEE], undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - Council campaign, 1976; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - Council Democratic primary, 1978; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - Council Democratic primary, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 25)
    - Council elections, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 27)
    - Council inauguration, 1977; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Council of D.C. vs. Rachel L. Clay, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Council primary, 1988; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - Council/management statistics, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Councilmembers 'Grid, Cuts, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Councilmembers' Grid, Taxes, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Council's Shopping Mall Bill, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Crawford, H.R., undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Crime-related stories, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 52)
    - Crisis, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 37)
    - Crivella, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 121, Folder 19)
    - CSX Real Property, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Cuffie, Lester, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - D.C. Agenda Project, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - D.C. Bankers Association, 1983 June 17; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - D.C. Bar, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - D.C. Bar, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 33)
    - D.C. Board of Education B10-425, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - D.C. Builders Association, 1983 February 14; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - D.C. Building Industry Association, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - D.C. Citizens Against Casino Gambling, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - D.C. Coalition Against the Death Penalty, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- Congressional voting reports, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- Crusade for Home Rule index cards, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- letters in envelopes and postcards, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- memos and draft letters, 1965 June-1966 March; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Folder 6)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- memos and draft letters, 1966 April-June; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- memos and draft letters, 1966 July; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Folder 8)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- memos and draft letters, 1966 August-1967 May; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Folder 9)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- memos and draft letters, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Folder 10)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- ministers and church group and petition, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Folder 5)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- newspapers, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 136, Folder 3)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- notepad, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- sermon, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 135, Folder 4)
    - D.C. Coalition of Conscience -- DCCC -- U.S. Senate bills, undated; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - D.C. Commission for Women Legislative Conference, 1983 October 15; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - D.C. Committee/Board of Elections and Ethics record, 1987 September 14; Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - D.C. Congress of Parent/Teacher Associations, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - D.C. Courts, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 77, Folder 53)
    - D.C. Death Penalty, Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 120, Folder 10)